Kurt & Courtney is a documentary, music film directed by Nick Broomfield.
After rocker Kurt Cobain's death, ruled a suicide, a film
crew arrives in Seattle to make a documentary.
Director Nick Broomfield talks to lots of people.
Portraits emerge: a shy, slight Kurt, weary of touring, embarrassed by fame, hooked on
heroin; an out-going Courtney, dramatic, controlling, moving from groupie to star.
Self - Interviewer, played by Nick Broomfield.
Self, played by Dylan Carlson.
Self (archive footage), played by Kurt Cobain.
Self, played by El Duce.
Self, played by Larry Flynt.
Self, played by Tom Grant.
Kurt & Courtney is a 1998 British documentary film by Nick Broomfield investigating the circumstances
surrounding the death of Kurt Cobain, and allegations of Courtney Love's involvement in it.
The film explores themes of singing, embryo,
living under the bridge, music rights.
The tone is emotional.